So you learned a lot about redux
Bu yzden Rydex hakknda ok ey reneceksiniz.
over the last lectures and modules. I emphasized that there are alternatives and I showed you some best
Son dersler ve modller zerinde, alternatiflerin bulunduunu vurguladm ve sana baz iyi uygulamalar
practices, good practices and ways to optimize your reducers and actions.
iyi uygulamalar ve redktrleri ve eylemleri optimize etme yollarn gsterdim.
You learned how to run asynchronous code with action creators like this one, how to use the redux-thunk
Bunu yapmak iin redux fonk katmannn nasl kullanlaca gibi, eylem oluturucularla ezamansz
middleware to do that,
kod altrmay rendiniz.
you learned how to combine reducers and how to use the redux dev tools to get insights into your store
Redktrleri nasl birletireceinizi ve maazanzla ilgili bilgi edinmek ve okumak iin X dev aralarn nasl
and even travel back in time if you want to.
kullanacanz rendiniz ve isterseniz zamannda geri yolculua kabilirsiniz.
These are all useful tools and redux is an extremely powerful library you'll see in a lot of react
ok sayda yeniden eyleme dnecektir imdi imdi Bergere cesurluumuza dnyor ve gelitirilmi biraz daha fazlas.
applications. We'll now also go back to our burger builder and enhance this a bit more
Bunlarn hepsi kullanl aralardr ve gevemek son derece gl bir ktphanede grleceiniz
by for example adding asynchronous code and in conjunction with redux, and chances are you'll also work
BI, rnein asenkron kod ekleyerek ve redoks ve ansla birlikte bir sonraki
with it in your next project.
projenizde onunla birlikte alacaksnz.
The basics of this module should have you well prepared.
Bu modln temelleri iyi hazrlanm olmaldr.